贾里德  妈的  你干什么呢
Ah! Jared, Jesus fuck! What are you doing?
抱歉  我就是
Sorry. I was...
我就是一个人冷静下情绪
I was just taking a quiet moment to collect myself.
你这堆的都是什么东西
What the hell is all this shit?
最近我的房客把我的东西都堆去
My tenant has been leaving my belongings
公寓后面的小路上了
in the alley behind my condo,
好给他的房客腾地方
to make more room for his tenants.
-你的房客还有房客吗  -是
- Your tenant has tenants? - Yeah.
他又用Airbnb转租了  所以如果你不介意
He's Airbnbing my Airbnb. So, if it's okay with you,
我可能还要多待几天
I might need to stay a little bit longer, um...
弗雷德搬来后  我可以从后面绕去卫生间
I can go around the back to get to the bathroom once Fred's here.
-他什么时候搬来  -我也想知道呢
- When's he moving in? - Wouldn't we all like to know.